{
  "mode": "text",
  "theme": "Capitals",
  "themeQuestion": "World Capitals",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "France",
      "answer": "Paris"
    },
    {
      "question": "Netherlands",
      "answer": "Amsterdam"
    },
    {
      "question": "United States",
      "answer": "Washington"
    },
    {
      "question": "Brazil",
      "answer": "Bras√≠lia"
    },
    {
      "question": "Japan",
      "answer": "Tokyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "Afghanistan",
      "answer": "Kabul"
    },
    {
      "question": "China",
      "answer": "Beijing"
    },
    {
      "question": "Denmark",
      "answer": "Copenhagen"
    },
    {
      "question": "North Korea",
      "answer": "Pyongyang"
    },
    {
      "question": "Portugal",
      "answer": "Lisbon"
    },
    {
      "question": "Thailand",
      "answer": "Bangkok"
    },
    {
      "question": "Venezuela",
      "answer": "Caracas"
    },
    {
      "question": "Peru",
      "answer": "Lima"
    },
    {
      "question": "Romania",
      "answer": "Bucharest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Morocco",
      "answer": "Rabat"
    },
    {
      "question": "Libya",
      "answer": "Tripoli"
    }
  ]
}
